<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nin Mining</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="contest_played">Contest Played</string>
    <string name="bids_won">Bids Won</string>
    <string name="playcoin_won">Money Won</string>
    <string name="my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="my_wallet">My Wallet</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="Withrawl_Note">Note :- Withdrawn Amount Will Take 24 Hrs To Process And Reflect In Your Bank Accounty.</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="info_amb">This is a user of the Next In Network who actively introduces other users to the Next In Network platform. The value of the Next In Network token increases as the community expands. This will be crucial for later updates of the mobile app where members engage in the transaction of goods and services with the earned Next In tokens. A ambassador can refer new users to join his/her earning team. For each active member in a team, the Keeper will earn an extra 25% base rate as a recommendation bonus. If a ambassador has 10 members in his/her earning squad and all of them are actively mining, the ambassador will earn an extra 10 x 25% = 250% NIN tokens of the base rate. This means that ambassador earn 25% of whatever their teammate mine every each day. Therefore, the key to making more Eagle tokens is to invite more new miners to join the mining team and remind them to log in daily for mining activation.</string>
    <string name="info_miner">This is a user of the Next In Network mobile app whose job is to confirm that he/she is basically not a “robot” daily. This user validates his/her presence every day as he/she must open the app every 24 hours to continue earning NIN tokens for free. A Miner can make the base rate of 2 NIN tokens per hour, which can be broken down to 1, 0.5, 0.25, 0.20, 0.15, 0.10, and 0 in line with the user base growth. By logingg into the mobile app every 24 hours and clicking the mining button, users participate.. many mining platforms, there is no need for a vast amount of energy to mine. In NiIN tokens We have simplified the method to make it possible on the smartphone. Anyone with a smartphone and the next In Network app can automatically earn an hourly mining rate by clicking the mining button. Each mining session automatically ends after 24 hours. Each miner is expected to open the app and click the mining button daily to keep earning.</string>
</resources>